Narrator: 1
M1: That giant rubber duck in the river was a PR stunt.
Narrator: 2
F1: An SUV is perfect if you’re looking for a comfortable ride with plenty of space.
Narrator: 3
M2: Pennsylvania is said to be one of the top places for UFO sightings.
Narrator: 4
F2: The CEO has called a meeting of all heads of department on Friday morning at 9.00.
Narrator: 5
F3: You can charge your phone from my laptop – it has a USB port.
Narrator: 6
M3: Want to be an astronaut? NASA could be looking for you!
Narrator: 7
F4: We’re both rubbish at DIY, so we’re getting someone in to decorate the house.
Narrator: 8
M4: GDP rose by 0.5% in the last quarter.
Narrator: 9
F5: The USP of our new batteries is that they last twice as long as all the others on the market.
Narrator: 10
F6: Thanks for your email. FYI my name is spelled J-A-N-E, not J-A-Y-N-E